{
    "subject": "resource/Safavid_dynasty",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Qazvin",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Safavid dynasty is Qazvin.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9058992266654968,
            "question": "What major historical dynasty had Qazvin as its capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8843672275543213,
            "question": "Name the capital city associated with the Safavid dynasty."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8709307312965393,
            "question": "What was the capital of the Safavid dynasty?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.827917218208313,
            "question": "The Safavid dynasty's capital was..."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5346009731292725,
            "question": "What city served as the administrative hub of the Safavid dynasty?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48135265707969666,
            "question": "In which city did the Safavid dynasty hold their court?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44836845993995667,
            "question": "Which empire's political center was located in Qazvin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38728004693984985,
            "question": "Where was the center of power for the Safavid Empire located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33616071939468384,
            "question": "Qazvin is known for being the..."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21721556782722473,
            "question": "Historically, what city served as the seat of government for the Safavids?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Safavid dynasty is Qazvin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9093_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Qazvin is known for being the...",
            "html": "dbpedia_9093_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was the center of power for the Safavid Empire located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9093_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which empire's political center was located in Qazvin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9093_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9093_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9093_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9093_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9093_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9093_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9093_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9093_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9093_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9093_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9093_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Qazvin was the capital of the Safavid dynasty for over forty years (1555-1598),\" which supports the statement that the capital of the Safavid dynasty is Qazvin."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}